Have you ever heard someone say, “breakfast is the most important meal of the day”, or give you advice about why it’s vital to start the day with a healthy breakfast?
你有没有听过别人说“早餐是一天中最重要的一餐”，或是有人建议你吃一顿健康的早餐对开启新的一天至关重要？
It seems that this feast, for many of us, is necessary for our day to start well, but is it really that important?
对我们很多人来说，这一餐似乎是顺利开启一天的必需品，但它真的有那么重要吗？
The word ‘breakfast’ comes from ‘breaking the fast’ – the idea of ending the period in which we didn’t eat during the night.
“早餐（breakfast）”这个词源于“打破禁食（breaking the fast）”，也就是结束夜间禁食状态的意思。
The regeneration process that takes place while we sleep consumes some of our natural food reserves to heal our bodies.
我们睡眠时身体会进行修复再生过程，这个过程会消耗体内储存的部分营养物质来修复身体机能。
Breakfast gives us an opportunity to replenish those depleted stores of things like protein and calcium.
早餐则为我们提供了补充蛋白质、钙等已消耗营养素的机会。
So, in that way, a healthy breakfast makes sense.
从这个角度来说，吃一顿健康的早餐确实是合理的。
There are also many often-quoted studies which seem to correlate a state of obesity with skipping breakfast.
此外，有许多被频繁引用的研究似乎表明，肥胖状况与不吃早餐有关联。
In fact, it leads many health experts to advise a healthy breakfast to not only regulate but also lose weight.
这也使得许多健康专家建议，吃一顿健康的早餐不仅有助于调节体重，还能帮助减重。
In a US study, 50,000 people were monitored over seven years, and those who ate a healthy breakfast were found to have a lower BMI, which seems to suggest that breakfast may indeed help people maintain a healthy weight.
美国一项针对5万人开展的七年追踪研究发现，坚持吃健康早餐的人群身体质量指数（BMI-body mass index）更低，这似乎说明早餐确实有助于人们维持健康体重。
But it might not be as simple as that.
但事情或许并没有这么简单。
Some experts, like Alexandra Johnstone, professor of appetite research at the University of Aberdeen, suggest those who skip breakfast might be less aware of healthy diets and nutrition, and people who eat breakfast might have a healthier lifestyle overall – exercising and not smoking, for example.
阿伯丁大学食欲研究教授亚历山德拉·约翰斯通等专家提出，不吃早餐的人可能本身就对健康饮食和营养学知识了解较少，而吃早餐的人通常有着更健康的整体生活方式——比如坚持锻炼、不吸烟等。
And with the rise in popularity of intermittent fasting to lose weight – there may also be some benefits to skipping breakfast.
此外，随着间歇性禁食减肥法的流行，不吃早餐或许也有其益处。
Intermittent fasting can improve blood sugar control, insulin sensitivity, and lower blood pressure.
间歇性禁食有助于改善血糖控制能力、提高胰岛素敏感性，还能降低血压。
So, while breakfast has its benefits, it might not be the most important meal.
因此，尽管早餐有其好处，但它或许并不是一天中最重要的一餐。
It seems that a healthy lifestyle with a balanced diet might be more important for many of us than just one single meal.
对我们很多人来说，保持健康的生活方式和均衡的饮食，可能比单独重视某一餐要重要得多。